SUJA SREEKUMAR

Full Stack Web Developer

CONTACT

suja.sreekumar@yahoo.com (857) 350 7204 sujasreekumar.com https://github.com/sujkid

SUMMARY

I am a full-stack web developer skilled in modern web technologies, a Computer Science graduate with 3 years of experience in developing applications in C++/VC++ in the medical domain with strong knowledge and experience in Analysis, Development, Testing and Troubleshooting in a variety of challenging environments.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Ruby On Rails Developer Code for Boston 05 / 2017 - Present

Web Development Immersive General Assembly 10 / 2016 - 01 / 2017

- Contributing to an open-source project to develop a tool requested by the City of Boston.
- Collaborating within a team using agile development workflow and widely accepted collaboration practices using Git.
- Built applications with object-oriented programming, data modeling, MVC frameworks and test-driven development.
- Worked in fast paced deadline driven environment
- View my projects at www.sujasreekumar.com

Software Engineer Network Systems and Technologies 2005 - 2008

- Expertise in Object Oriented Analysis/Design and C++ development, skilled at progressing from problem statement to well-documented design.
- Involved in analysis, design and coding the replacement of the AT communication framework using COM interfaces.
- Solid management skills, demonstrated proficiency in leading and mentoring individuals to maximize levels of productivity, while forming cohesive team environments.
- Proven ability to meet agreed project and customer satisfaction targets.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Technology Computer Science Cochin University of Science and Technology 2001 - 2005

SKILLS

Javascript
Ember.js
NodeJS
JQuery

HTML5

CSS3
Bootstrap
Sass

Ruby Agile/Scrum
Rails C++
PostgreSQL Java

VC++/MFC